myjellybean.com 2012-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Myjellybean.com

#### Myjellybean.com has produced this policy statement to reflect our commitment to our users' privacy.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act) became effective on April 21, 2000 . The regulations apply to the online collection of personal information from children 12 years and younger. The Act spells out what we, as website operators, must include in our privacy policy, when and how to seek verifiable consent from a parent and what responsibilities we, as website operators, have to protect and secure children's privacy and safety online.

COPPA applies to individual identifiable information about a child (12 or younger) that is collected online, such as full name, home address, email address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact a child. The Act also applies to other types of information, such as hobbies, interests and user information gathered through the use of cookies and other methods of tracking, when they are tied to individually identifiable information.

Myjellybean.com is a strong advocate of Internet privacy and embraces the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We therefore take strong measures to protect the privacy and safety of our users.

**Myjellybean.com - No User Registration Required for General Site**

Myjellybean.com does not require users of our general site register or provide any contact/demographic information prior to surfing our articles, games and other features. Unlike some other major sites for kids and teens, you can surf most areas of Myjellybean.com without "logging on" or being asked to share any personal information.

**No Third-Party Sharing**

Certain areas of Myjellybean.com, including the message boards, street team, and sweepstakes, ask users for personal information. We do not disclose our users' personal information (including email address) to anyone, at any time, for any reason.

**Chat Boards**

Myjellybean.com has chat (message) boards that require user registration, via email address. This information is used to get in touch with our members when necessary. Myjellybean.com allows users to opt-out of receiving communications from us in the initial registration form. If a user wishes to opt-out after completing the registration form, they can do so by changing the preferences in their user profile when they are logged into the chat boards.

We also ask new registrants for their date of birth. This information is used to screen under-13 users. We do not permit automatic registration by users identifying themselves as age 12 and under. (The Myjellybean.com message boards also use a registration system cookie check. This saves a cookie onto the user's computer if an age under 13 is entered upon registration. Subsequent registration attempts will be failed, no matter what age is entered). For 12 and unders, we obtain permission from their parent/guardian before they can be fully registered. We do this by requiring them to complete and sign a permission form, which must be faxed or mailed to our offices within a 7-day period.

Myjellybean.com's chat board rules are strongly enforced. These rules prohibit unwanted behaviors that we deem to be unsafe or inadvised for our members, including the harrassment of any individual or group; expressions of bigotry, hatred or abuse; profanity or nasty language aimed against others; threats of harm to anyone; sexually explicit material in posts or uploaded images; and advocating illegal conduct or participation in fraudulent schemes. In addition, the Myjellybean.com staff reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any thread for any reason.

Our chat boards are monitored for compliance with the board rules by a team of teen volunteer moderators and experienced Myjellybean.com staff. Our moderators assist in ensuring that our users do not divulge personal information. Anyone who tries to reveal, or ask for, personal information will have their posts deleted and be sent a strong warning. If the problem persists with the same user, their IP address could be permanently blocked and future access denied to the website from that IP address.

Users should be aware that any posts and conversations on an Internet message board becomes public information. You should NOT disclose any personally identifiable information (such as your name, telephone number, address, school name, parent's workplace, and so on). Your username is the only identity you should have, and that is how people should know you on the Internet.

**Contests & Sweepstakes**

Myjellybean.com hosts regular contests and sweepstakes in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as full name, e-mail and mailing address). This information is used strictly to contact entrants when necessary (such as informing them they have won) and to fulfill prizing. Contact information collected for contests is deleted once winners have been confirmed and prizes have been shipped. In cases where prizing is fulfilled by third-party companies (contest sponsors), we require them to delete contest winners' personal information after the prizes are sent.

**Covet Program**

Myjellybean.com runs a membership-only COVET Program to connect teens with companies wishing to give away products and services. Members of our COVET Program must register and provide certain personal details to join, including but not limited to date of birth, email address, mailing address, number of Facebook friends. This information is used to screen and communicate with members, and to fulfill any prizing a member may win in the Program. Date of birth information is used to screen under-13 users. We do not permit registration by users identifying themselves as age 12 and under. When we run COVET Program contests and sweepstakes, this site may ask members for additional information. Members agree that upon request, they will provide a photo of themself with any product they win, for promotional use on this website, and will write a review of any product they win on the COVET Program Blog on this website. Members further agree that the name and email information collected during their COVET Program registration may be shared with third-party sponsors of the COVET Program. 

**E-Mail**

Myjellybean.com offers email "@ myjellybean.com" in partnership with a third-party company, Everyone.net. We do not allow children known to be under the age of thirteen (13) to register for our email services. Everyone.net collects non-identifying and aggregate information for marketing services, and shares the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties. No personal information is shared with third-parties by Myjellybean.com or Everyone.net. For more information on Everyone.net's Privacy Policy, please visit this link.

**Outbound Links**

Our site contains links to other sites. Although Myjellybean.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other sites, we do our best to screen all sites accessible from Myjellybean.co to ensure that they comply with our standards.

**Street Team**

Myjellybean.com has a street team of members who love our site, and want to help spread the word about us. However, we do not condone email spam and our team members are strongly advised against it. Membership is open to registrants aged 13 and over. We accept members from every country, but only Street Teamers living in the U.S. or Canada are eligible to win prizes in street team contests. Information collected from street team members at registration (including name and email address) is used by Myjellybean.com staff to contact street team members when necessary.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on Myjellybean.com are delivered to members by Womensforum.com, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to Myjellybean.com, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to control the delivery of ads to you on this site.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Terms Of Service**

In addition to reviewing this Agreement, please read our Terms Of Service, which governs the use of Myjellybean.com, including without limitation participation in its bulletin boards, forums, blogs, street team, and other features provided by Myjellybean Inc. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to its terms and conditions as well.

**Contacting Us**

For Media Enquiries, please [email us here](mailto:promotions@myjellybean.com?subject=Media%20Enquiry).

Please visit our [Contact Us page](http://www.myjellybean.com/corporate/contact-us) for other contact information.

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, or have any other questions for or about Myjellybean.com, you can get in touch with us at [this email](mailto:jellybe@jellybe.com), or by snail mail at:

Myjellybean Inc.   
PO Box 65171   
RPO Chester   
Toronto, ON   
M4K 3Z2   
Canada
